翻译 kk
翻译 飞少爷
时间轴  Chenfan
朋友 你技艺精湛
You're an artist, my friend.
校对  Trilce
3815米
3,815 metres.
校对  Chenfan
即使受过军事训练 你的射击距离也只有他的一半
You need military training to make a shot at even half that distance.
后期  Chenfan
-有一个人  -亚历山大·杜根
- There is one guy. - Alexander Duggan
曾是狙击好手
was an outstanding sniper.
总监  Chenfan
但他死了
But he's dead.
他去了阿富汗 然后再也没回来
He went to Afghanistan. The entire unit was wiped out.
已故 已故 已故
已故 麦克·鲍德温队长 已故 已故
但是死无对证
But there was no body.
若有意参与热门影视剧的字幕译制
让自己的名字出现在字幕开头
远鉴字幕组招新群 483552098
招募英语翻译 欢迎您的加入
欢迎关注 b站up主 远鉴字幕组
公众号 远鉴影视
微博 @远鉴字幕组v @远鉴的小跟班v
微博资源博主 @苏苏IFA
不太对劲
Something's not right.
伊莎贝尔告诉我 你想看一份二级绝密文件
So, Isabel tells me you want to have a look at a STRAP 2 file,
-你觉得它能帮你找到豺狼  -是的
- because you think it'll help you find the Jackal? - Yes.
文件给我吧 欧斯
I'll take the file, Osi.
哈尔克罗 这边请
This way, Mr. Halcrow.
-我们得谈谈  -现在是地毯式找内鬼
- We need to talk. - It a full blown mole hunt.
-保罗 我不想看见她  -没人想跟你说话
- I don't want her here, Paul. - No one's trying to speak to you.
-我想跟我丈夫和孩子说  -求你了 进去吧
- I'm trying to talk to my husband... - Please, just go back inside, yeah.
你要回家吗
Are you coming home?
还是说 你要住在你该死的前妻家
Or are you staying here with your fucking ex-wife?
去死吧 暴君
Fuck you, you tyrant!
塔林是我们唯一的机会 他却失手了
Tallinn was our one chance and he missed.
乌达查向全世界保证
UDC wants the world to know...
资流终将流淌
that River will flow.
是查尔斯吧
lt's Charles, isn't it?
突发新闻 警方正在寻找该男子
如果你有该男子的任何线索 请拨打以下号码
是他吗
lt's him?
-你明天还能回来吗  -能
- Are you coming tomorrow? - Yes.
因为
Because now...
我他妈要知道真相
I want the fucking truth!
瓦尔马林岛  克罗地亚
安保B队
Security team Bravo
已控制目标船只
now has control of subject vessel
正在进行船上搜查 收到
and conducting onboard search. Copy.
安保D队为B队的搜查提供空中监视
Security team Delta providing overwatch to Bravo search team.
你可以抱怨 可以哀号
♪ You can holler, you can wail
可以扭动 可以挣扎
♪ You can swing, you can flail
你可以像破帆船一样 随波逐流
♪ You can thump like a broken sail
但我绝不会抛下你
♪ But I'll never give you up
如果我就这样弃你不顾
♪ If I ever give you up
我的心也定会失落
♪ My heart will surely fail...
-运输船已到达 一切安全  -开始行动
- Delivery boat's here. All clear. - Proceed.
你可以扭动 可以挣扎
♪ You can swing, you can flail
你可以摧毁我残存的理智
♪ You can blow what's left of my right mind
我不在意
♪ I don't mind. ♪
怎么回事
What happened?
早上好
Morning.
他们只知道 你有机会但是失手了
You know, as far as they're concerned, you had a shot and you missed.
他们只在乎这个
That's all they care about.
资流将在48小时后发布
River launches in 48 hours.
你在乎吗
Does that concern you at all?
你应该在乎
Because it should.
我可不是来这里度假的
I'm not here on holiday.
有些花朵
♪ Some flowers
从未绽放 不见天日
♪ Never get to bloom and see the day
有些花朵
♪ Some flowers
得过且过
♪ Are content to wish their lives away
有人崛起
♪ Some may rise
有人跌倒
♪ And some may fall
但唯有
♪ But only
你让
♪ You make
天堂般的美好
♪ Heaven
变得真实
♪ Seem it's true
唯有
♪ So, only
你能
♪ You can
告诉他们
♪ Tell them
真实的我
♪ This is who I am
改编自弗雷德里克·福赛斯的小说
真实的我
♪ This is who I am
没有欺骗
♪ No lie
看清
♪ Know that
真实的我
♪ This is who I am ♪
豺狼的日子
第一季 第九集
在我小时候
When I was a little boy,
我外婆 我妈妈的妈妈
my grandmother, my mum's mother,
是希伯来人
from Hebron,
她告诉我 受人敬仰与遭人唾弃 往往只在一念之间
told me there's a fine line between being revered and being spat on.
而现在
And here we are,
天朗气清
it's a beautiful day...
没人骂我
and no one's spitting on me.
他们只是想杀我
They're just trying to kill me.
他们可以尝试 但永远无法实现
They can try, but they'll never do it.
话虽如此
But...
如果我真的遭不测
if I don't make it...
向我保证 你要继续推动资流
promise me... you'll make River happen.
乌勒 我可以答应你 但我们心知肚明 我做不到
Ulle, I could promise, but we both know I'd be lying.
董事会不喜欢资流
The board hates River.
他们容许你发布资流 是因为他们怕你
They do what you want because they're afraid of you.
你是说 他们敬畏我
You mean in awe of me.
是 我就是这个意思
Yes, that's what I meant.
他们不敬畏我
They're not in awe of me.
所以 你必须好好活着
So, I suppose you'll just have to stay alive, won't you.
他们到底为何牺牲
更新：格林尼治标准时间12:00 2013年6月17日
战争交织着残酷和英雄主义 有人证明了顽强不屈的精神可以抵抗战争中的至暗时刻
鲍德温上尉曾深入阿富汗危险地带 执行秘密行动 却在简易爆炸装置袭击中痛失整支部队
他的事迹显露出 士兵为了追求正义所做出的巨大牺牲
在本次独家采访中 鲍德温上尉讲述了他的部队在执行消灭塔利班高级领导人任务时经历的惨痛事件
军情六处 303部门
数据库搜索 麦克·鲍德温上尉
鲍德温上尉 感觉怎样
Captain Baldwin, how you feeling?
他妈的糟透了
Fucking terrible.
肺癌
Lung cancer...
是因为赫尔曼德的焚烧坑吧
from the burn pits in Helmand, is that right?
你队里的八个人都死在那了
Eight of your men died there, didn't they?
节哀顺变
I'm so sorry that happened.
对你来说 那肯定是地狱般的经历
That must have been a hellish experience for you.
关于亚历山大·杜根 你有什么能告诉我的
What can you tell me about Alexander Duggan?
你不是医生
You're not a doctor.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是军情六处的
I'm with Six.
我有几个问题要问你
I need to ask you some questions...
关于在赫尔曼德发生了什么
about what happened in Helmand.
都在报告里写着 我觉得你应该离开了
It's all in the report. I think you should leave now.
做不到 除非你回答我的问题
I can't. Not until you've answered my questions.
我不和军情六处说话 出去
I'm not talking to MI6. Get out.
我要叫护士
I want the nurse.
没问题 我们谈完 护士就会来
Of course. The nurse will come once we've had our chat.
我需要更多吗啡
I need more morphine.
那就快点说
Then talk quickly.
斯普利特  克罗地亚
船只稳定性 让船保持平稳的物理原理
简单安装 基础原理 稳定性概述
装配稳定器的十佳船只
云台
云台 一种机械稳定装置
查询航班
出发地 克罗地亚 普拉
目的地 西班牙 加的斯
哪位
Yep?
比安卡 请进
Come in, Bianca.
我最近在尝试养植物 但养什么死什么
I've been trying to get into plants. But I keep killing everything.
这个习惯可不好改
Ah, tough habit to break.
而且 这事无聊透顶
Also... it's boring as fuck.
我得告诉你 豺狼案件的最新情况
I want to update you on the Jackal investigation.
我找到了更多杜根的信息
I have some more information on Duggan.
显然 他以前是个独行者
Apparently, he was a loner.
先坐下
Sit down.
和他关系好的 只有他的观测手
The only person he was close with was his spotter,
加里·科布
a guy called Gary Cobb.
如果杜根还活着
So if Duggan's alive,
科布可能也活着
it's possible that Cobb is alive, too.
是有可能 但几率很低 没有证据
It's possible, but it's unlikely. There's no evidence.
但这是个线索
But it's a lead.
说实话 比起线索 更像是你的观点
It's a theory more than a lead, let's be honest.
那我希望去验证我的观点 看看我能找到什么
Well, I'd like to test that theory and see if I can find anything.
这不可能了
I don't think that's going to be possible.
为什么
Why?
因为我要终止调查了
Because I'm closing the investigation.
你不能这么做
You can't do that.
我不能凭直觉做决定
I can't make decisions based on hunches.
-有人因此丧命  -死的人太多了
- People have died. - Too many people.
但我的资源有限
But I have a limited amount of resources
为了一个人 不值得损失这么多
and one man is not worth all this loss.
那我们就这么认输吗
So we just admit defeat?
别总是把事情想得那么绝对
You really must learn to think in a less binary way.
我就快抓到他了
I am closing in on him.
比安卡 该决定和你 和你快要抓到他都无关
It's not about you, Bianca, and your need for closure.
是为了大局
This is about the big picture.
大局利益
The greater good.
我只需要再多一点时间
I just need a little more time.
别管这事了
And I need you to move on.
如果我不呢
And if I don't?
你不会喜欢这个问题的答案
I don't think you'll like the answer to that question.
我是欧斯·哈尔克罗 请留言
'Hi, this is Osita Halcrow, please leave a message.'
欧斯 我是比安卡
Osi, it's Bianca.
你在哪 给我回个电话
Where are you? Call me, please.
你听说了吗
Have you heard?
听说什么
What?
你今天没看见欧斯吧
You haven't seen Osi today, have you?
没
No.
我听说什么了
Have I heard what?
就是...
It's...
-为什么又让我来 卡弗  -快接啊
- Why am I here again, Carver? - Pick up, pick up, pick up.
关于为什么信息会泄露出去
Well, we still have unanswered questions
我们还有疑问
about information getting into the wrong hands.
关于诺曼 关于白俄罗斯
About Norman, about Belarus...
-关于匈牙利  -我们都讨论过了
- ..about Hungary. - We've been over that.
你没告诉我们
What you haven't told us,
为什么你的手机记录显示 你收到了美国号码的短信
is why your phone records showed you received texts from a number in the United States.
但我们去查这些短信
But when we looked for the texts,
发现已经被你删掉了
you had deleted them.
加的斯  西班牙
传教士 告诉我
♪ Preacher man, go tell me
护照
他在哪安息
♪ Where his body lies
孩子 在河边坐下吧
♪ Sitting down by the river Now, child
我们接二连三跌倒
♪ One by one we tumble
我们接连不断坠落
♪ One by one we fall
亲爱的 要是我有办法
♪ If I had a solution, now, honey
努丽娅
Nuria?
怎么下床啦
What are you doing out of bed?
嗨 小家伙
'Hi, little boy.
我的小宝贝
'Hi, my little one.
我好想你
'I've missed you so much.'
宝贝 我真的太想你了
You can't imagine how much I've missed you, my love.
你的飞机要飞去哪
Where's your plane going?
宝贝 它要去哪
Where's it going, little one?
这样吧 你 我 和妈妈
I'll tell you what, why don't you, me and mummy...
我们一起坐上你的飞机
we get on your plane...
飞去很远的地方
and we go somewhere far away.
就我们三个
Just the three of us.
但你要当驾驶员
You'll have to fly it...
因为我有点累了
'cause I'm a bit tired.
而且妈妈应该也不会开飞机
And I don't think your mummy knows how to fly a plane.
也不一定
Although, with mother...
你妈妈可有本事了
with your mother you never know.
你来开飞机
'You fly the plane.'
卡利托斯机长
'Captain Carlitos.
该睡觉了 小家伙
'I think it's your bedtime, little one.
我来把你抱上床 舒舒服服地睡
'Let's get you in there, let's get you snuggled up.
真乖
'Good boy.
'Good boy.'
睡吧
Sleep...
乖乖睡吧
Sleep now.
你是谁
Who are you?
明知故问
You know who I am.
这是真的吗
Is this real?
你什么意思
What d'you mean?
这个
This.
还有这个
有哪个是真的吗
Is any of this fucking real?
有吗
Hm?
我来告诉你你是谁
Let me tell you who you are.
你是个骗子
You're a liar.
所以现在
So, now...
告诉我全部真相 因为这是你最后的机会
now you tell me the truth because it's your last chance.
看着我
Look at me.
一直看着我
Don't stop looking at me.
这是你吗
Is this you?
是的
Yeah.
你是为了钱杀人吗
D'you kill people for money?
是的
Yeah.
-说出来  -说什么
- Say it. - Say what?
把这句话说出来
Say the words.
说出来
我为了钱杀人
I kill people for money.
没听清 什么
Sorry, what?
听不清 我听不清
No te oigo. I can't hear you.
你说什么
What did you say?
我为了钱杀人
I kill people for money.
再说一遍
Say it again.
-我为了钱杀人  -好好听听你自己在说什么 再说一遍
- I kill people for money. - Listen to yourself and say it again.
我为了钱杀人
I kill people for money.
-再来  -我为了钱杀人
- Again. - I kill people for money.
-再说一遍  -我为了钱杀人
- Say it again! - I kill people for money.
我为了钱杀人 这就是你想听的吗
I kill people for money. Is that what you wanna hear?!
够了吗
Is that enough?!
听够了吗
Is it enough?!
不够
It's not.
不过我们现在能谈一谈了
But now we can have a conversation.
原来你还没死啊
So you're not dead.
为什么一直不接我电话
Why have you not been answering your phone?
我很忙
I've been busy.
我发现杜根和他的观测手加里·科布是形影不离的好兄弟
I found out that Duggan and his spotter Gary Cobb were inseparable.
-所以呢  -所以呢
- So? - So?
你肯定知道 行动已经终止了
This operation has been closed down. As I'm sure you know.
这到底是怎么回事 欧斯
I'm sorry, what is going on, Osi?!
显然有人根本不在乎豺狼会不会杀掉乌达查
Someone clearly doesn't give two shits if the Jackal kills UDC-
我说了你别生气 你给我闭嘴
Don't take this personally, but please shut the fuck up!
不
No.
我做不到
I can't.
我
I...
我不想谈这些
I-I'm not having this conversation.
你无视我没关系
Look, you can ignore me all you want
但我就是很失望
but I'm just disappointed.
我还以为我身边都是蠢货
I thought out of all the fucking dickheads around here,
只有你与众不同
you... were the one that was different.
在我们这行 与众不同可不吃香
In this job, different is inadvisable.
欧斯
Osi?
比安卡：我在外面
比安卡 2分钟前来电
-安吉拉在家吗  -楼上
- Is Angela home? - She's upstairs.
一切都还好吗
Is everything OK?
不好
No.
诸事不顺
No, nothing's "OK" right now.
我一直以来
I've always been...
都很清楚自己想要什么
clear about what I want
-以及为什么要这么做  -又是在说你的工作
- and-and why I'm doing it- - About your work?
-对 但是  -我不想和你谈你的工作 比安卡
- Yeah, but everyth -I don't wanna talk about your work, Bianca.
好吧
OK.
因为那是丈夫该做的事
Because that's what a husband does.
但我不知道你现在把我当什么了
And I don't know what I am to you right now.
-我不知道我们的未来在哪  -我知道我的未来在哪
- I don't know where we're headed. - I know where I wanna be headed.
是啊 我也知道我的
Yeah, I know where I wanted to be headed, too.
-但想法和实际截然不同  -我想你了
- But what we want and what's actually possible, they are two very different - I miss you.
我也想你
Yeah, I miss you, too.
我也知道我就像个噩梦
And I know I'm a nightmare.
而这时候 你应该说
And this is where you say,
你不是噩梦 比安卡 你好极了
"You're not a nightmare, Bianca. You're great."
-你就是噩梦  -但你仍然爱我
- You are a nightmare. - But you love it though.
不爱吗
No?
-你爱我  -我确实爱你
- You love me. - I do love you.
-我也爱你 这难道不是最重要的吗  -不
- And I love you, and isn't that what matters? - No.
比安卡 你不是为我们的事来的
Bianca, you're not here... you're not here because of us.
你来这 是因为你工作上出了问题
You're here because of a problem at work.
不全是这样
That's-That's not... That's not completely true.
你怀上贾思敏的时候很年轻
Look, you were really young when you had Jasmine.
-你那时候还很年轻  -没错
- OK, you were really young... - Yeah, exactly.
-就要做那样的选择  -是的
- ..to make that choice. - Exactly.
但并不是当时选完就一劳永逸了
But it's not a one-time choice.
你必须担负起家庭责任
OK, you've got to keep choosing it every day.
不是遇到困难才来
Not just when things aren't working out for you.
而是 你真的想和我们一起生活
But bec... because it's what you really want.
如果安吉拉看到你在这
Look, if... Y'know, if Angela sees you here, she's...
她会大发雷霆的
she's gonna lose her shit, so...
你觉得你能把工作和家庭完全分开吗
Did you think you could live two parallel lives?
说实话 我从没想过这个
I honestly never thought about it.
但我打算金盆洗手了
But I'm gonna stop.
结束了
It's over. Done.
不干了
Finished. It's done.
-真的吗  -对 真的
- Really? - Yeah, really.
真的
Yeah.
但是呢
But?
查尔斯
Charles.
还有一件事
There's one more job...
我必须完成
that I have to finish.
我他妈就知道
I fucking knew it.
我只需要24小时
All I need is 24 hours.
你去哪
Where you going?
喝杯咖啡
I need a coffee.
阿尔瓦罗
Alvaro.
嘿
Hey!
你气色不错
You're looking great.
查尔斯在家吧
Charles is here, right?
我想和他一起吃个午饭
I want to grab lunch with him.
阿尔瓦罗 现在不是时候
Alvarb, now is not the time.
努丽娅 听着
Nuria, look...
我给他争取了一个很好的机会
I've got a great opportunity for him.
改天再说吧 好吗
Another day, okay?
不行
No.
我不能再等了
lt can't be another day!
你怎么了
What's wrong with you?
我怎么了
What's wrong with me?
你到底怎么了
What's wrong with you?
没什么
Nothing...
查尔斯得来 我保证过的
Charles needs to come, l've given my word.
向谁保证过
Given your word? To who?
吉米 那个古巴人
Jimmy, the Cuban guy.
吉米·泰赫罗
Jimmy Tejero?
你跟他说了什么
What are you doing speaking to him?
就是我在做的事
Just stuff I'm working on...
还有 我需要查尔斯的帮助
and lneed Charles' help.
你跟他说了查尔斯的什么事
What have you told him about Charles?
我能跟他说什么 什么也没说
What am I going to tell him? Nothing.
我只说了 查尔斯是潜在的优质合伙人 投资人
Just that Charles could be a good partner or investor.
得了吧
Fuck me.
别担心 我不会搞砸的
Girl, don't worry. l won't fuck this up.
我只说了钱的事
I've only talked about money.
听着
Look
我只跟他说了钱的事
I've only spoke about money...
我本可以把其他事都说出来的
and I could've spoken about all the other stuff
但我没有
and l didn't.
怎么了
What's wrong?
阿尔瓦罗跟我说 他和吉米·泰赫罗聊过
Alvaro just told me that he's been talking to Jimmy Tejero.
吉米·泰赫罗 我的天
Jimmy Tejero, por Dios!
谁是吉米·泰赫罗
Who's Jimmy Tejero?
他是个黑帮老大
He's a fucking gangster.
很危险
He's dangerous.
他是整个加的斯最坏的人
The worst person you can meet in Cadiz!
-阿尔瓦罗谈到我了吗  -对
- Alvaro was talking about me? - Yeah.
我不相信阿尔瓦罗
I don't trust Alvaro.
他答应了吉米什么事
He's... He's made some promises to Jimmy,
因为他知道
because he knows that...
你很有钱
that you have money and...
也知道你是干什么的 我不知道还有什么
and what you do, and... I don't know what else!
如果吉米知道了你
If Jimmy knows about you,
-我们就有危险了 还有卡利托斯  -好了好了
- we're not safe. And Carlito. - Whoa, whoa, whoa.
看着我
Look at me.
我受不了了
I can't do this...
看着我
Look at me.
你得想想办法
You've got to do something, please.
看着我
Look at me.
不论他是谁 不论发生了什么事
Whoever this is, whatever this is...
我都会处理好的
I'm gonna make this OK.
好
OK.
好吗
Yeah?
好
Yeah.
阿尔瓦罗
Alvaro?
-查尔斯  -嗨
- Charles. - Hi.
嗨
Hi.
我听说你需要我帮忙
So, I hear you need some help?
-是的  -是吗  -对
- Yeah. - Yeah? - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
好吧
OK, uh...
是这样
Listen...
我找到了一个绝佳的商机
I have a... a good business opportunity
对你 对我 对所有人来说都是
for you, for me, for everybody.
好 我何时何地能帮你
OK, so where and when d'you need me?
-所以你会来吗  -是的
- So you're coming? - Yeah.
-你会来  -对
- You're coming? - Yeah.
太好了
Okay.
你知道维多利亚吗
Well, you know La Victoria?
-知道  -那个海滩
- Yeah. - The beach.
你知道那个有餐厅的大酒店吗
You know the big hotel with the restaurant...
-塞拉酒店  -海滩上那个
- Oh, the Sierra. - ..in the beach.
塞拉 塞拉酒店 对
Sierra. Hotel Sierra, yeah.
-好 几点  -一点怎么样
- OK, what time? - Mm, one?
一点 在塞拉酒店
One o'clock at the Sierra.
一点 塞拉酒店 你和我
One, Sierra Hotel, you and me?
嗯
Yeah.
-行吗  -行
- OK? - OK.
太爱你了
I could kiss you!
谢谢
Thank you.
非常感谢
Very much, very much.
还有 别担心
And don't worry that...
我们有好酒 会很开心 不用你花钱
we have wine, good time, and you pay nothing, eh?
我来请客
This one I pay.
瓦尔马林岛  克罗地亚
玛乔丽 你想说什么
So, Marjorie, what's on your mind?
董事会想让你推迟一个月发布资流
The Board wants you to postpone River for one month.
绝对不行
Absolutely not.
达格豪斯的股价在直线下降
The DagHaus share price is in freefall.
过去三天 你亏了十二亿美元
In the last three days you've personally lost 1.2 billion dollars.
这是媒体制造的恐慌
This is media driven panic.
达格豪斯远比资流重要
DagHaus is much more than River.
我们的技术和应用 对世界经济至关重要
Our technologies and applications are fundamental to the world economy.
但是
But...
有一点 我要说清楚
let me make one thing... perfectly clear.
资流能创造公平的竞争环境
If a level playing field, like the one River will make possible,
意味着 像你我这样的超级富豪
means that super rich people like you and me
必须舍弃我们的游艇和私人飞机
will have to give up our yachts and private jets
这么做 年轻人才能拥有光明未来
so that young people can have a decent future...
对我而言
well, personally,
我非常乐意这么做
that's something I embrace with open arms.
好吧
OK.
如果你明天发布资流
If you launch tomorrow,
董事会将全体辞职
the entire board will walk.
我是得到他们的明确同意才来的
I am here with their explicit approval.
如果你们都想离开
Well, if you all wanna go...
那请便吧
I guess you'll just have to go.
你真的不考虑推迟发布吗
You really won't consider a postponement?
明天发布资流
River launches tomorrow.
纽约  美国
谢谢
Thank you.
-杰里米 很高兴再次见到你  -我也是 蒂莫
- Jeremy. Good to see you again. - Pleasure as always, Tim.
-请坐  -谢谢
- Please. - Thank you.
我知道 很抱歉我没有什么好消息
Yes, yes. I'm sorry I don't have better news.
但是 我和我同事 商务大臣
But, um... Well, I did speak to my colleague, the Business Secretary,
谈过让欧洲法庭颁布禁令阻止资流发布的可能性
about the possibility of the European courts placing an injunction to stop the release of River.
但实话说
But, um, well frankly,
他觉得这事行不通
he's not optimistic,
我也这么觉得
and neither am I.
抱歉
Sorry.
要想成就一番伟业
"When we would accomplish great things,
最佳策略是 依靠一套不为外人所知的机制运作
the best policy is to work by an engine... which the world never sees."
没错
Yes.
-我忘了这话是谁说的  -嗯
- I forget, who said that? - Well, it's...
这话不假 说得对极了
It's very true. Rather brilliant.
可能是我自己说的
Oh! Maybe it was me?
是的
Yes.
是的 可能是你说的
Yes, maybe it was you.
豺狼是我们最后的希望
So, all we have left is our Hail Mary, the Jackal.
没错
Yes, quite.
他现在在哪
Where is the Jackal now?
加的斯  西班牙
查尔斯
Charles.
好久不见
Since a long time.
-太久没见了  -你好吗
- Too long. - How are you?
-很好  -是吗
- Fine. - Yeah!
-你呢  -你看起来很好 身材保持得不错
- You? - You look very well. You look trim.
谢谢
Thank you.
太感谢你帮我临时安排了
Thank you so much for sorting this last minute.
-你想钓多久  -几个小时吧
- For how long you want to fish? - Just a couple of hours, I think.
我就想 放空一下
Yeah, I just need to... disconnect a little.
-好 那你好好放松  -嗯
- So, you have a big relax. - Yeah.
-水况很好 钓完把钥匙放在老地方就行  -好 我会的
- Water's perfect. So, just leave the keys in the usual place. - Great, will do.
-好  -谢了 吉尔莫
- OK. - Thanks, Guillermo.
-祝你好运  -再见
- Good luck. - Bye.
再来一瓶
Another bottle.
年轻人
So kid.
这个英国人总是迟到吗
this Englishman always arrives late or what?
没有
No
别担心 他马上就到
No, don't worry. He's coming soon.
他说了他想要
He said he wants to
抓住这次机会的
take advantage of this opportunity.
他知道这单生意很棒
He knows this business is great.
我们谈的是多少钱啊
What amount of money are we talking about?
是几千吗
ls it thousands?
还是几百万
Or is it millions?
哥们 几百万
Man, millions, millions.
这家伙非常有钱
This guy is filthy rich.
他从哪赚到这些钱的
Where does he get it?
钱啊
The money...
国际金融
...lnternational finance.
国际金融 是吧
International finance?
吉米
Jimmy?
他中枪了
He's been shot!
子弹从哪飞来的
Where did that come from?
斯普利特  克罗地亚
于是我向雾中走去
♪ So I walked into the haze
迎面万丈肮脏波浪
♪ And a million dirty waves...
诺曼 你技艺精湛
You were an artist, Norman.
我看见你躺在那
♪ Now I see you lying there
像一个漏气的气垫
♪ Like a lilo losing air...
漆黑的礁石 岸边的浪花
♪ Black rocks and the shoreline surf
依然是我无法忍受的夏天
♪ Still dead summer I cannot bear
把这里的恐惧忘却
♪ Forget the horror here
终将锈蚀 化为尘土
♪ It's future rust And it's future dust
资流终将流淌 泰迪·瓦尔德里奇
资流将在12小时后发布
乌达查将于明天发布资流
我是你脑海中燃烧的怒火
♪ I'm the fury in your head
是你记忆中不散的孤魂
♪ I'm the ghost In the back of your head
我就在此
♪ 'Cause I am ♪
我是你脑海中燃烧的怒火
♪ I'm the fury in your head
我是你枕边熊熊的烈焰
♪ I'm the fury in your bed
风力雷达
风速
天气预报
斯普利特 早上9:30
是你记忆中不散的孤魂
♪ I'm the ghost In the back of your head
我就在此
♪ 'Cause I am. ♪
我为了钱杀人 这就是你想听的吗
I kill people for money. Is that what you wanna hear?!
听够了吗
Is that enough?!
不够
No, it's not.
国际新闻 黑帮成员在西班牙餐厅内被狙击手射杀
古巴黑帮成员吉米·泰赫罗在西班牙加的斯遇刺身亡
狙击手从远处射击 击毙了坐在海滨餐厅里的泰赫罗
登录
国际情报公告
吉米·泰赫罗遭遇暗杀 狙击手的精准射击
犯罪集团头目吉米·泰赫罗被精准射杀 难以追查
这颗致命子弹从极远距离射出 体现出超高射击精度和技巧
尽管西班牙警方展开了全面调查 但仍未发现任何与枪手有关的明确证据
令这起专业且目标明确的暗杀事件蒙上了神秘面纱
精准射杀 体现出超高射击精度和技巧
"Sniper-style shot. The operation displayed a high degree of precision and skill."
过去这几年 我一直想拍草原百灵鸟
So, I've been trying to get a shot of the Calandra Lark for the past couple of years.
你知道草原百灵鸟吗 一种很漂亮的鸟
Do you know the Calandra Lark? It's a very beautiful bird.
我听说普拉夫尼克岛上有一对在繁衍
I heard that there's a breeding pair on Plavnik Island.
为什么要去普拉夫尼克岛是你的事
Why you want to go to Plavnik is your business.
你付钱 我载你去就是了
You paid, I'll take you.
能停在这吗
Can we stop here, please?
你想停在这
You want to stop here?
对 我好像在空中看到了
Yes, I think I've seen something up there.
对 看到了
Yeah, I've seen something.
那是什么
What's that?
我的装备
It's a lot of kit.
还有五个小时
Five hours.
你打算就这么一直躺着吗
Are you planning on staying in bed till then?
我昨晚睡得很不好
I had a terrible night.
我今天应该不能去游泳了
I don't think I can face swimming today.
乌勒 你不能在你人生中最重要的这一天破例
Ulle, you're not breaking your routine on the biggest day of your life.
游泳对你有好处 能让你头脑清醒
A swim does you good. It clears your head.
你总这么说
You always say that.
快去吧
Come on.
-那是谁的船  -博格丹的
- Whose boat is that? - Bogdan's.
我从没见过博格丹来这里钓鱼
I haven't seen Bogdan stop to fish there before.
船在两英里外
It's outside the two mile perimeter.
我知道 但还是盯着点
I know, but keep an eye on it.
明白
Roger that.
-早上好 先生  -早
- Good morning, sir. - Morning.
一切准备就绪
Everything's ready.
和以前一样 您的保镖会随时伴您左右
As always, your minder will be next to you at all times and-
-能直接出发吗  -规矩他都知道
- Can we just go? - He knows the drill.
遵命
Yes, sir.
委托人即将走出别墅
Principal exiting the villa now.
收到
Roger that.
所有人注意 我是0A
All call signs, this is Zero Alpha,
委托人已上路 前往塞拉
Principal on route. Heading to Sierra.
所有人保持警惕 无人机监视
All stay vigilant, Drone overwatch focused on...
完毕
..report. Out.
D1安保小队
Security team Delta One providing-
-一切正常 周边安全  -谢谢
- All clear. Perimeter secure. - Thank you.
行动 游泳愉快 先生
Proceed. Enjoy your swim, sir.
委托人正在下水
Principal exiting now.
收到
Roger that.
0A和委托人在塞拉下水点
Zero Alpha with principal at Sierra drop off.
呼叫0号控制 请求指示
Zero control, copy for Green.
我是0号 可以行动
This is Zero, you are green to go.
该死
Fuck.
拜托
Come on.
博格丹的船没动
'Bogdan's boat's not moved.'
巡逻队的摩托艇正前往察看
Jet ski from patrol unit on its way to check.
我是D1
This is Delta One,
我发现有可疑活动
I have spotted suspicious activity near Sector-
拜托
Come on.
无人机已就位
Roger! Overwatch on task.
摩托艇遇袭 博格丹船上有枪手
Jet ski down! Gunman on Bogdan's boat.
有狙击枪
Sniper rifle.
D1中枪
Delta one is down.
-有枪手  -一级警报
- There is an active shooter... - Code Red!
船上有狙击手
Sniper on the boat!
一级警报
Code Red!
快让武装小组去保护他
Get armed units towards him!
让他潜入水下
Get him under water!
注意水面
Eyes on the water!
潜下去
Get down! Get down!
潜入水中 不要露头
Down! Down! Down! Under the water and stay down!
一
One...
二 三
two, three...
七 八
..seven, eight,
九 十
nine, ten.
-天哪  -保镖中枪了
- Oh, fuck! - Minder's down!
潜入水中
Stay under the water, sir!
Get down under the water!
潜下去
No, down! Down!
一 二
One, two...
三 四
three, four...
找到你了
There you are.
委托人中枪
Principal is down,
principal is down.
让医疗队前往塞拉
Team medic to Sierra location,
0号控制 通知急救队 立即撤离
Zero control, alert emergency medical services for immediate exfil.
快速反应一组 我们盯住枪手了
QRF One, we have eyes on active shooter.
枪手正快速逃离
Shooter is making a fast exfil.
这最终的一搏
♪ Raced for the last time
我知道你从不肯低头
♪ Well, I know you'll hold Your head up high
但我们已无话可说
♪ But it's nothing we have to say
眼泪也已流干
♪ There's nothing in our eyes
仍有事悬而未决
♪ But there's something in the air
我眼中仍有情意
♪ Something in my eye
我与你共舞太久
♪ I've danced with you too long
还有话未曾出口
♪ There's something I have to say
还有事悬而未决
♪ There's something in the air
还有余情未了
还有余事未竟
♪ There's something in the air. ♪